<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>BigFood2307</author>
    <version>1.0.0.4</version>

    <title>
        <en>Dynamic Field Prices</en>
        <de>Dynamische Feld Preise</de>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en>
			<![CDATA[
Makes Field prices more interesting. It might make sense to look out for good deals instead of always buying the closest land.
Some NPCs are more greedy than others and their economic situation changes over time influencing the prices as well.
An extra 10% is added when buying or selling a field. This will strongly limit field flipping.
Prices change once per day. The difference to the base price in percent is shown when buying land.

For more detailed information check out the project on github. (Google FS22_DynamicFieldPrices)

Thanks to the Additional Field Info mod for showing a way to display more information in the map screen.

Changelog:
- v1.0.0.1:
* Moved display in map view to make it compatible with Additional field info.
* Uses i18n for display
- v1.0.0.2:
* Adjusted mod description
* New icon
- v1.0.0.3
* Moved display to the right slightly to adjust for longer words in german
- v1.0.0.4
* added pt/br translation
]]>
        </en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Feldpreise werden interessanter gestaltet. Möglicherweise macht es mehr Sinn, nach einem guten Deal zu suchen, statt immer das benachbarte Land zu kaufen.
Manche NPCs sind gieriger als andere. Außerdem ändert sich ihre finanzielle Situation, was den Preis mit der Zeit ebenfalls verändert.
Eine Provision von 10% wird bei jedem Kauf/Verkauf angerechnet. Field Flipping wird dadurch stark ausgebremst.
Preise ändern sich einmal am Tag. Der Unterschied zum Grundpreis in Prozent wird beim Landkauf angezeigt.

Detailiertere Informationen sind im Github Projekt zu finden. (Google FS22_DynamicFieldPrices)

Danke an den Additional Field Infos Mod für das Aufzeigen einer Methode um weitere Informationen in der Karte anzuzeigen.

Changelog:
- v1.0.0.1:
* Anzeige im Map View verschoben für Kompatibilität mit Additional field info.
* Nutzt i18n in der Anzeige
- v1.0.0.2:
* Mod Beschreibung angepasst
* Neues Icon
- v1.0.0.3
* Anzeige leicht nach rechts verschoben om längere deutsch Worte zu unterstützen.
- v1.0.0.4
* pt/br Übersetzung hinzugefügt
]]>
		</de>
	</description>
        
	<l10n filenamePrefix="i18n/locale"/>
		
    <iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="DynamicFieldPrices.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
